Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Beadle Administration Records 1916-1968
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Development
  - Expense reports, 1963-1967 (Box 381, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Development Committee, 1961 (Box 381, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1958-1968 (Box 382, Folder 1)
  - History, Department of, 1962-1967 (Box 382, Folder 2)
  - Humanities, Division of, 1963-1967 (Box 382, Folder 3)
  - Law School, 1961-1967 (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - Library, Advisory Faculty Committee to plan new science library, 1938-1968 (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - Library, Advisory Faculty Committee to plan (new science), membership, 1964-1966 (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - Library building, background on H.E.W. (Health, Education and Welfare) proposal, 1965-1966 (Box 382, Folder 7)
  - Library building, background material used by Mr. E. H. Levi in Regenstein presentation, 1962-1965 (Box 382, Folder 8)
  - Library building, background material used by Mr. E. H. Levi in Regenstein presentation, 1962-1965 (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - Library building, Joseph Regenstein Library, 1965-1967 (Box 383, Folder 2-6)
  - Library building, proposed new, 1960-1964 (Box 384, Folder 1-4)
  - Library building, proposed new, "the Library Brochure," 1965-1967 (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - Library, Graduate School, Edward A. Henry, Librarian, 1957-1965 (Box 384, Folder 6)
  - Regenstein Library, 1965-1966 (Box 384, Folder 7-8)
  - Special gifts prospects, 1961 (Box 384, Folder 9)
  - Special gifts prospects, 1961-1963 (Box 385, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University, development manual, 1961 (Box 385, Folder 2)
  - Vice-President of Development, 1961-1964 (Box 385, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Invitations
  - Invitations, 1961-1968 (Box 385, Folder 4-7)
  - January 1961 (Box 386, Folder 1)
  - February 1961 (Box 386, Folder 2)
  - March 1961 (Box 386, Folder 3)
  - April 1961 (Box 386, Folder 4)
  - May 1961 (Box 386, Folder 5)
  - August 1961 (Box 386, Folder 6)
  - September 1961 (Box 386, Folder 7)
  - October 1961 (Box 386, Folder 8-9)
  - November-December 1961 (Box 387, Folder 1)
  - January 1962 (Box 387, Folder 2)
  - February 1962 (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - March 1962 (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - April 1962 (Box 387, Folder 5-6)
  - May 1962 (Box 387, Folder 7)
  - June-August 1962 (Box 387, Folder 9)
  - September 1962 (Box 387, Folder 10)
  - October 1962 (Box 387, Folder 11)
  - October 1962 (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - November 1962 (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - December 1962 (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - January 1963 (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - February 1963 (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - March 1963 (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - April 1963 (Box 388, Folder 7)
  - May 1963 (Box 388, Folder 8)
  - June 1963 (Box 388, Folder 9)
  - July 1963 (Box 388, Folder 10)
  - August 1963 (Box 388, Folder 11)
  - September 1963 (Box 388, Folder 12)
  - October 1963 (Box 389, Folder 1)
  - November 1963 (Box 389, Folder 2)
  - December 1963 (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - January-March 1964 (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - April 1964 (Box 389, Folder 5)
  - May 1964 (Box 389, Folder 6)
  - June 1964 (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - July-August 1964 (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - September 1964 (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - October 1964 (Box 390, Folder 4-6)
  - November-December 1964 (Box 390, Folder 7)
  - January 1965 (Box 391, Folder 1)
  - February-March 1965 (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - April 1965 (Box 391, Folder 3-4)
  - May 1965 (Box 391, Folder 5-7)
  - June 1965 (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - July-August 1965 (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - September 1965 (Box 392, Folder 3-4)
  - October 1965 (Box 392, Folder 5-6)
  - November-December 1965 (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - January 1966 (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - February 1966 (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - March 1966 (Box 393, Folder 3)
  - April 1966 (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - May 1966 (Box 393, Folder 5)
  - July-August 1966 (Box 393, Folder 6)
  - September 1966 (Box 393, Folder 7-8)
  - October 1966 (Box 394, Folder 1-2)
  - November 1966 (Box 394, Folder 3-4)
  - December 1966 (Box 394, Folder 5)
  - January 1967 (Box 394, Folder 6)
  - February 1967 (Box 394, Folder 7)
  - March 1967 (Box 395, Folder 1-2)
  - April 1967 (Box 395, Folder 3-4)
  - May 1967 (Box 395, Folder 5)
  - June 1967 (Box 395, Folder 6)
  - July-August 1967 (Box 396, Folder 1)
  - September 1967 (Box 396, Folder 2)
  - October 1967 (Box 396, Folder 3-4)
  - November-December 1967 (Box 396, Folder 5)
- Series V: Trustees
  - Board of Trustees, Aldis, Graham, 1946-1967 (Box 397, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, Alumni Committee, 1963 (Box 397, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees, Committee on Alumni, 1963 (Box 397, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees, Committee on the Organization and Function of the Board, 1961 (Box 397, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, Committee on the University Press (Special Visiting), 1963 (Box 397, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees and Committees, agendas, 1964-1965 (Box 397, Folder 6-7)
  - Board of Trustees, Development Committee, minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 397, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, Field, Marshall, 1952-1966 (Box 397, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, Graham, Phillip Leslie, 1949-1963 (Box 397, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees, Library Committee, 1963-1966 (Box 398, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, lists of committee memberships, 1961-1968 (Box 398, Folder 2-3)
  - Board of Trustees, Lloyd, Glen Alfred, 1953-1968 (Box 398, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Trustees, McConnell, Fowler Beery, 1947-1962 (Box 398, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, McDonough, John Justin, 1956-1961 (Box 398, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees, meetings, 1961-1964 (Box 399, Folder 1-7)
  - Board of Trustees, meetings, 1965-1968 (Box 400, Folder 1-5)
  - Board of Trustees, Nicely, James Mount, 1950-1964 (Box 400, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, Randall, Clarence Belden, 1936-1967 (Box 401, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Trustees, Wilson, Robert Erastus, 1945-1966 (Box 401, Folder 3)
  - Trustee Faculty Dinner, 1951-1968 (Box 401, Folder 4-7)
  - Trustee Faculty dinner, 1963-1968 (Box 402, Folder 1-5)
  - Trustee Faculty Dinner, speeches, 1960-1964 (Box 402, Folder 6-9)
  - Trustees, 1961 (Box 402, Folder 10)
  - Trustees, Ad Hoc Committee on Alumni Representation on Board, 1958-1967 (Box 403, Folder 1)
  - Trustees Faculty Dinner, speeches, 1964-1968 (Box 403, Folder 2-6)
  - Trustees Fund, 1961-1966 (Box 403, Folder 7-9)
  - Trustees Fund, number 1, luncheon billings, 1951-1961 (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, general, 1963-1967 (Box 404, Folder 2-4)
  - Trustees and Officers, articles of incorporation by-laws, 1965 (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Trustees, requests for information, 1944-1965 Folder 7: Trustees Secretary's docket, 1952-1968 (Box 404, Folder 6)
  - Trustees Secretary's docket, 1952-1968 (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, speakers for Board luncheons and dinners given by the President, 1961-1967 (Box 405, Folder 2-8)
  - Trustees, speakers for Board luncheons and dinners given by the President, 1968 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, "Who's Who,"1961-1965 (Box 406, Folder 2-3)
  - Trustees, "Who's Who," latest entries, 1961-1962 (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Trustees' wives, 1961-1966 (Box 406, Folder 5)
  - Trustees' wives fund, 1958-1967 (Box 406, Folder 6-7)
- Series VI: Appointments and Budgets
  - Appointments and Promotions, Subcommittee on, 1963-1964 (Box 407, Folder 1)
  - Appointments, Subcommittee to Study Reappointment, Promotion and Tenure, policies and practices, 1959-1963 (Box 407, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 407, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1962-1964 (Box 408, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget, 1964-1966 (Box 409, Folder 1-3)
  - Budget, 1965-1967 (Box 410, Folder 1-3)
  - Budget, 1966-1968 (Box 411, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 412, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 413, Folder 1)
  - Budget, cost analysis, 1966-1967 (Box 413, Folder 2)
  - Budget, Dean's statements, 1967-1968 (Box 413, Folder 3)
  - Budget, development and planning, public relations, alumni, 1966-1968 (Box 413, Folder 4)
  - Budget estimates, 1963-1965 (Box 413, Folder 5-6)
  - Budget estimates, 1966-1967 (Box 414, Folder 1)
  - Budget extension, 1967-1968 (Box 414, Folder 2)
  - Budget, includes work prepared by Carl Holm, 1966-1967 (Box 414, Folder 3)
  - Budget information, 1964-1967 (Box 414, Folder 4)
  - Budget Narrative, Divisions and Schools, 1965 (Box 414, Folder 5)
  - Budget notes, closing on fiscal 1965 (Box 414, Folder 6)
  - Budget, Oriental Institute, 1967-1968 (Box 414, Folder 7)
  - Budget, Orthogenic School, 1967-1968 (Box 414, Folder 8)
  - Budget projections, 1966-1967 (Box 414, Folder 9)
  - Budget revision, 1967-1968 (Box 414, Folder 10)
  - Budget savings, 1967 (Box 414, Folder 11)
  - Budget, Social Sciences, 1967-1968 (Box 415, Folder 1)
  - Budget, Student Services, 1967-1968 (Box 415, Folder 2)
  - Budget, year end closing, 1967-1968 (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - College, Divisions and Professional Schools of the University of Chicago, academic budget, 1964 (Box 415, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller Baptist Theological Union, 1959-1965 (Box 415, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller confidential, 1961-1966 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller's statement, 1958-1961 (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller's statement, 1961-1964 (Box 417, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller's statement, 1964-1967 (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Preliminary regular budget income statements, 1966 (Box 419, Folder 1)
  - Regular budget, Vice-President for Planning and Development, 1966-1967 (Box 419, Folder 2)
  - Revised budget, planning and development, 1967 (Box 419, Folder 3)
- Series VII: Oversize Materials
  - Development, Sketch plan, the University of Chicago, preliminary report, 1962 (Box 420)
  - Development, Charles Brenton Huggins, M.D., Nobel Laureate, Physiology and Medicine, book, 1966 (Box 421)
  - Development, The Science Library, the University of Chicago, book, circa 1966 (Box 421)
  - Development, scrapbook of University brochures, publications, and information, 1951-1954 (Box 421)
  - Development, Deferred Giving Program, scrapbook, 1962 (Box 422)
  - Development, Graduate School of Business, gift opportunities, circa 1961 (Box 422)
  - Development, Biological Sciences Research Building, circa 1955 (Box 423)
  - Development, Medical and Biological Research Associates Program, circa 1955 (Box 423)
  - Development, Preview of Tomorrow's Discoveries in Medicine, circa 1950s (Box 423)
  - Development, sketch plan, the University of Chicago, 1962 (Box 423)
  - Development, "To Make the Oldest the Newest," circa 1960 (Box 423)
  - Urban renewal, blueprints, 1961-1962 (Box 424)
  - Urban renewal, development project, blueprints and legal documents, 1961-1966 (Box 424)
  - Urban renewal, newspaper clippings, 1958-1960 (Box 424)
  - Urban renewal, newspaper clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 424)
  - Urban Renewal: People, Politics and Planning, edited by Jewel Bellush and Murray Hausknecht, book, 1967 (Box 424)
  - Urban renewal, photographs, ca. 1960 (Box 424)